[
  {
    "id": 1101,
    "question": "salimos",
    "answer": "We"
  },
  {
    "id": 1102,
    "question": "lados",
    "questionDetails": "Hay salidas por los cuatro lados de la iglesia.",
    "answer": "sides, sided",
    "answerDetails": "There are exits on all four sides of the church."
  },
  {
    "id": 1103,
    "question": "cambiado",
    "questionDetails": "Me encontré con Fernando y lo vi muy cambiado desde el accidente.",
    "answer": "changed",
    "answerDetails": "I ran into Fernando and he has changed a lot since the accident."
  },
  {
    "id": 1104,
    "question": "espacio",
    "questionDetails": "Se invirtió fuera del espacio de estacionamiento.",
    "answer": "space, room, area",
    "answerDetails": "He reversed out of the parking space."
  },
  {
    "id": 1105,
    "question": "pruebas",
    "questionDetails": "Leyó el informe de pruebas.",
    "answer": "evidence",
    "answerDetails": "You read the evidence report."
  },
  {
    "id": 1106,
    "question": "ponga",
    "questionDetails": "Ponga su mano sobre la mesa.",
    "answer": "put, place, lay",
    "answerDetails": "Put your hand on the table."
  },
  {
    "id": 1107,
    "question": "vengan",
    "questionDetails": "Diles que vengan a la mesa.",
    "answer": "come",
    "answerDetails": "Then go tell them to come to the table."
  },
  {
    "id": 1108,
    "question": "pesar",
    "questionDetails": "Sentimos un gran pesar cuando nuestro perro murió el mes pasado.",
    "answer": "sorrow",
    "answerDetails": "We felt great sorrow when our dog died last month."
  },
  {
    "id": 1109,
    "question": "suya",
    "questionDetails": "Con permiso, señor. La chaqueta que está en la silla, ¿es la suya?",
    "answer": "yours, hers, theirs",
    "answerDetails": "Excuse me, sir. Is that jacket on the chair yours?"
  },
  {
    "id": 1110,
    "question": "verme",
    "answer": "watch me"
  },
  {
    "id": 1111,
    "question": "cumpleaños",
    "questionDetails": "El cumpleaños de mi madre es mañana.",
    "answer": "birthday",
    "answerDetails": "My mother’s birthday is tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "id": 1112,
    "question": "darte",
    "answer": "Give"
  },
  {
    "id": 1113,
    "question": "acaban",
    "questionDetails": "En lugares como el que acaban de destruir.",
    "answer": "just",
    "answerDetails": "At sites like the one you just destroyed."
  },
  {
    "id": 1114,
    "question": "experiencia",
    "questionDetails": "Usted debe tener la experiencia necesaria en la gestión de la salud.",
    "answer": "experience",
    "answerDetails": "You should have the necessary experience in health management."
  },
  {
    "id": 1115,
    "question": "dejamos",
    "questionDetails": "Usamos lo que queremos y dejamos el resto.",
    "answer": "leave",
    "answerDetails": "We take what we want and leave the rest."
  },
  {
    "id": 1116,
    "question": "termina",
    "answer": "Ends"
  },
  {
    "id": 1117,
    "question": "damos",
    "questionDetails": "Nos damos toda la prisa que podemos.",
    "answer": "we",
    "answerDetails": "We have all the haste we can."
  },
  {
    "id": 1118,
    "question": "leer",
    "questionDetails": "Me encanta leer sobre culturas extranjeras.",
    "answer": "read",
    "answerDetails": "I love reading about foreign cultures."
  },
  {
    "id": 1119,
    "question": "cierra",
    "questionDetails": "Cierra la puerta o entra.",
    "answer": "close, shut, shuts down",
    "answerDetails": "Either close the door or come in."
  },
  {
    "id": 1120,
    "question": "metió",
    "answer": "Got"
  },
  {
    "id": 1121,
    "question": "diste",
    "questionDetails": "Vendió la propiedad que le diste.",
    "answer": "gave",
    "answerDetails": "He sold the villa you gave him."
  },
  {
    "id": 1122,
    "question": "quedas",
    "questionDetails": "Si trabajas, te quedas.",
    "answer": "stay",
    "answerDetails": "You work out, you stay."
  },
  {
    "id": 1123,
    "question": "contado",
    "questionDetails": "Sus días al mando de la empresa están contados.",
    "answer": "numbered",
    "answerDetails": "His days as the head of the company are numbered."
  },
  {
    "id": 1124,
    "question": "vuelto",
    "answer": "change"
  },
  {
    "id": 1125,
    "question": "llevan",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo tipos así llevan semejantes estuches.",
    "answer": "carry, lead, bear",
    "answerDetails": "Only creeps carry such big cases."
  },
  {
    "id": 1126,
    "question": "quizá",
    "questionDetails": "Quizá no se crean lo que oyen.",
    "answer": "maybe",
    "answerDetails": "Maybe they don’t believe what they hear."
  },
  {
    "id": 1127,
    "question": "ponen",
    "questionDetails": "Lo ponen en el congelador una hora.",
    "answer": "put, lay",
    "answerDetails": "Put it in the freezer for an hour."
  },
  {
    "id": 1128,
    "question": "preparado",
    "questionDetails": "Después de 2 meses de clases, creo que estoy preparado para tomar el examen de conducir.",
    "answer": "ready, preparation, poised",
    "answerDetails": "After two months of lessons, I think I’m ready to take the driving test."
  },
  {
    "id": 1129,
    "question": "aquel",
    "questionDetails": "¿De qué vestido hablas?-Aquel que está en la vidriera.",
    "answer": "that one",
    "answerDetails": "Which dress are you talking about?-That one in the window."
  },
  {
    "id": 1130,
    "question": "quiso",
    "questionDetails": "Yo quise salir, pero ella quiso quedarse en casa.",
    "answer": "she wanted, he loved",
    "answerDetails": "I wanted to go out, but she wanted to stay home."
  },
  {
    "id": 1131,
    "question": "salida",
    "questionDetails": "El amplificador tiene una salida de 40 megavatios.",
    "answer": "output, exit, departure",
    "answerDetails": "The amplifier has an output of 40 megawatts."
  },
  {
    "id": 1132,
    "question": "ayúdame",
    "answer": "Help me"
  },
  {
    "id": 1133,
    "question": "quita",
    "questionDetails": "Quita la venda y ve.",
    "answer": "removes",
    "answerDetails": "It removes the bandage and you go."
  },
  {
    "id": 1134,
    "question": "dejaste",
    "questionDetails": "¿Dejaste tu cartera en el trabajo?",
    "answer": "did you leave, you dropped",
    "answerDetails": "Did you leave your wallet at work?"
  },
  {
    "id": 1135,
    "question": "culo",
    "questionDetails": "Fue operado el culo.",
    "answer": "ass, arse, butt",
    "answerDetails": "He had ass surgery."
  },
  {
    "id": 1136,
    "question": "llegando",
    "questionDetails": "El tren ya está llegando.",
    "answer": "arriving, coming, reaching",
    "answerDetails": "The train is arriving."
  },
  {
    "id": 1137,
    "question": "bienvenido",
    "questionDetails": "Organizamos un marco de actividades que usted es Bienvenido a unirse.",
    "answer": "welcome",
    "answerDetails": "We arrange a framework of activities which you are welcome to join."
  },
  {
    "id": 1138,
    "question": "pregunto",
    "questionDetails": "Me pregunto como de lejos está el cielo.",
    "answer": "wonder, ask",
    "answerDetails": "I wonder how far this sky goes."
  },
  {
    "id": 1139,
    "question": "mete",
    "questionDetails": "Nadie se mete conmigo.",
    "answer": "messes, stuffs, tuck",
    "answerDetails": "Nobody messes with me!"
  },
  {
    "id": 1140,
    "question": "entera",
    "questionDetails": "Una alfombra entera de ellos.",
    "answer": "entire, whole, learns",
    "answerDetails": "An entire carpet of them."
  },
  {
    "id": 1141,
    "question": "destino",
    "questionDetails": "No creo en el destino. Creo que tomamos nuestras propias decisiones.",
    "answer": "fate, destiny",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t believe in fate. I think we make our own choices."
  },
  {
    "id": 1142,
    "question": "últimos",
    "questionDetails": "Estos son sus últimos recuerdos.",
    "answer": "latest, last, past",
    "answerDetails": "These are her latest memories."
  },
  {
    "id": 1143,
    "question": "mandó",
    "questionDetails": "Esto es lo que me mandó.",
    "answer": "sent, commanded, instructed",
    "answerDetails": "These are what he sent me."
  },
  {
    "id": 1144,
    "question": "tratando",
    "questionDetails": "Estaba tratando de parar a mi amigo.",
    "answer": "trying, dealing, treating",
    "answerDetails": "I was trying stop my friend."
  },
  {
    "id": 1145,
    "question": "miren",
    "questionDetails": "Miren en el balcón.",
    "answer": "look, looky",
    "answerDetails": "Look up in the balcony."
  },
  {
    "id": 1146,
    "question": "completamente",
    "questionDetails": "Queremos cosas completamente distintas de nuestras vidas.",
    "answer": "completely, entirely, thoroughly",
    "answerDetails": "We want completely different things out of life."
  },
  {
    "id": 1147,
    "question": "nerviosa",
    "questionDetails": "Estaba nerviosa por la noche.",
    "answer": "nervous, nerve, jumpy",
    "answerDetails": "She was nervous at night."
  },
  {
    "id": 1148,
    "question": "puedas",
    "questionDetails": "Que al menos, tú puedas dormir.",
    "answer": "can",
    "answerDetails": "You can sleep, at least."
  },
  {
    "id": 1149,
    "question": "hacerme",
    "answer": "make me"
  },
  {
    "id": 1150,
    "question": "vuelvas",
    "questionDetails": "Esperan que vuelvas muy pronto.",
    "answer": "come back, again",
    "answerDetails": "They hope you come back real soon."
  },
  {
    "id": 1151,
    "question": "parado",
    "questionDetails": "La Avenida parece un estacionamiento. El tráfico está completamente parado.",
    "answer": "stopped",
    "answerDetails": "The avenue looks like a parking lot. Traffic is completely stopped."
  },
  {
    "id": 1152,
    "question": "unidos",
    "answer": "United, attached, together"
  },
  {
    "id": 1153,
    "question": "libertad",
    "questionDetails": "Tener libertad para hacer algo.",
    "answer": "freedom, liberty",
    "answerDetails": "To have the freedom to do something."
  },
  {
    "id": 1154,
    "question": "san",
    "answer": "San, St, Saint"
  },
  {
    "id": 1155,
    "question": "hubieras",
    "questionDetails": "Si te hubieras ido.",
    "answer": "had",
    "answerDetails": "If you had let go."
  },
  {
    "id": 1156,
    "question": "haz",
    "questionDetails": "El granjero esparció una haz de paja para que se acostara la vaca.",
    "answer": "bundle",
    "answerDetails": "The farmer spread out a bundle of straw for the cow to lie down on."
  },
  {
    "id": 1157,
    "question": "hayas",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando hayas escuchado el rugido de las olas .",
    "answer": "beeches, you",
    "answerDetails": "Where beeches listen to the roar of waves."
  },
  {
    "id": 1158,
    "question": "necesitaba",
    "questionDetails": "Stephanie fue al supermercado porque necesitaba comprar papel higiénico.",
    "answer": "she needed",
    "answerDetails": "Stephanie went to the supermarket because she needed to Buy Toilet Paper."
  },
  {
    "id": 1159,
    "question": "complicado",
    "questionDetails": "Un sistema estéreo complicado.",
    "answer": "complicated, tricky",
    "answerDetails": "A complicated stereo system."
  },
  {
    "id": 1160,
    "question": "honor",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo el honor de presentarles al premio Nobel de Medicina.",
    "answer": "honour",
    "answerDetails": "It is my honour to introduce the Nobel Prize winner for Medicine."
  },
  {
    "id": 1161,
    "question": "vueltas",
    "questionDetails": "Los coches están dando las últimas vueltas de entrenamiento.",
    "answer": "laps, turns, spins",
    "answerDetails": "The cars are now on their final laps of practice."
  },
  {
    "id": 1162,
    "question": "perdió",
    "questionDetails": "Jugué al ajedrez con Sandra. Naturalmente, perdió.",
    "answer": "she lost",
    "answerDetails": "I played chess with Sandra. Naturally, she lost."
  },
  {
    "id": 1163,
    "question": "genial",
    "questionDetails": "El concierto estuvo genial. Deberías haber venido con nosotros.",
    "answer": "great, terrific, brilliant",
    "answerDetails": "The concert was great. You should have come along."
  },
  {
    "id": 1164,
    "question": "respuesta",
    "questionDetails": "Existe una considerable variación de especies en la respuesta del estómago al alcohol.",
    "answer": "response, answer, reply",
    "answerDetails": "There is considerable species variation in the stomach’s response to alcohol."
  },
  {
    "id": 1165,
    "question": "espalda",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca te daré la espalda.",
    "answer": "back",
    "answerDetails": "I will never turn my back on you."
  },
  {
    "id": 1166,
    "question": "toque",
    "questionDetails": "El chef añadió su toque especial.",
    "answer": "touch, tap, hint",
    "answerDetails": "The chef added his special touch."
  },
  {
    "id": 1167,
    "question": "pasamos",
    "questionDetails": "Pasamos una hora en el hotel.",
    "answer": "spent, had",
    "answerDetails": "We just spent an hour at the hotel."
  },
  {
    "id": 1168,
    "question": "línea",
    "questionDetails": "Suprima la segunda línea del tercer párrafo.",
    "answer": "line",
    "answerDetails": "Delete the second line of the third paragraph."
  },
  {
    "id": 1169,
    "question": "bebé",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando lo tienes, lo logras, bebé.",
    "answer": "baby",
    "answerDetails": "You either got it or you don’t, baby."
  },
  {
    "id": 1170,
    "question": "arma",
    "questionDetails": "Echa un vistazo a mi nueva arma.",
    "answer": "weapon",
    "answerDetails": "Check out my new weapon."
  },
  {
    "id": 1171,
    "question": "muerta",
    "answer": "dead person"
  },
  {
    "id": 1172,
    "question": "vestido",
    "questionDetails": "No me siento nada elegante, porque no me di cuenta de que debía llevar vestido para este evento.",
    "answer": "gown",
    "answerDetails": "I feel so underdressed because I did not realize that I had to wear a gown to this event."
  },
  {
    "id": 1173,
    "question": "visita",
    "questionDetails": "Tu hijo me hizo una visita la semana pasada.",
    "answer": "visit, tour",
    "answerDetails": "I had a visit from your son last week."
  },
  {
    "id": 1174,
    "question": "imagínate",
    "questionDetails": "Imagínate si lo hiciéramos juntos.",
    "answer": "imagine",
    "answerDetails": "Imagine if we hosted it together."
  },
  {
    "id": 1175,
    "question": "muertos",
    "questionDetails": "Los muertos me han dado sus respuestas.",
    "answer": "dead, dead ones, killed",
    "answerDetails": "The dead have given me their answers."
  },
  {
    "id": 1176,
    "question": "cumplir",
    "questionDetails": "Todos los muebles de segunda mano deben cumplir con las nuevas regulaciones.",
    "answer": "comply, fulfill, satisfy",
    "answerDetails": "All second-hand furniture must comply with the new regulations."
  },
  {
    "id": 1177,
    "question": "hacerte",
    "questionDetails": "Solo era una broma; no quise hacerte llorar.",
    "answer": "make you",
    "answerDetails": "It was just a joke; I didn’t mean to make you cry."
  },
  {
    "id": 1178,
    "question": "darme",
    "answer": "Me"
  },
  {
    "id": 1179,
    "question": "terrible",
    "questionDetails": "Vinimos corriendo apenas supimos de la terrible noticia.",
    "answer": "dreadful, awful, appalling",
    "answerDetails": "We came running as soon as we heard the dreadful news."
  },
  {
    "id": 1180,
    "question": "ponte",
    "questionDetails": "Ponte en el suelo.",
    "answer": "get",
    "answerDetails": "Get on the floor."
  },
  {
    "id": 1181,
    "question": "nacional",
    "questionDetails": "Esta política puede haber sido en el interés nacional.",
    "answer": "national, domestic, nationwide",
    "answerDetails": "This policy may have been in the national interest."
  },
  {
    "id": 1182,
    "question": "memoria",
    "questionDetails": "Es necesario destruir la memoria en el arte.",
    "answer": "memory",
    "answerDetails": "It is necessary to destroy memory in art."
  },
  {
    "id": 1183,
    "question": "peso",
    "questionDetails": "Continúa llevando el peso del mundo sobre sus hombros.",
    "answer": "weight",
    "answerDetails": "He continues to carry the weight of the world on his shoulders."
  },
  {
    "id": 1184,
    "question": "dura",
    "answer": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 1185,
    "question": "tuviera",
    "questionDetails": "Podía saltar como si tuviera fuego en los pies.",
    "answer": "had",
    "answerDetails": "She could skip like she had fire in her toes."
  },
  {
    "id": 1186,
    "question": "conocen",
    "questionDetails": "Lo conocen por las canciones que compuso.",
    "answer": "know, familiar",
    "answerDetails": "You all know him from the songs he’s written."
  },
  {
    "id": 1187,
    "question": "calor",
    "questionDetails": "El calor feroz del sol.",
    "answer": "heat, hot, warmth",
    "answerDetails": "The fierce heat of the sun."
  },
  {
    "id": 1188,
    "question": "plata",
    "questionDetails": "El oro es más valioso que la Plata.",
    "answer": "silver",
    "answerDetails": "Gold is more valuable than silver."
  },
  {
    "id": 1189,
    "question": "muchachos",
    "questionDetails": "El sargento convierte a los muchachos en soldados.",
    "answer": "young men",
    "answerDetails": "The sergeant turns young men into soldiers."
  },
  {
    "id": 1190,
    "question": "muchacho",
    "questionDetails": "Pasamos la noche fuera con los muchachos.",
    "answer": "boy",
    "answerDetails": "We spent the night out with the boys."
  },
  {
    "id": 1191,
    "question": "sigues",
    "questionDetails": "Sigues en el mismo canal.",
    "answer": "still",
    "answerDetails": "Still the same channel."
  },
  {
    "id": 1192,
    "question": "hagamos",
    "questionDetails": "Depende de lo que hagamos con ella.",
    "answer": "do",
    "answerDetails": "It depends what we do with it."
  },
  {
    "id": 1193,
    "question": "canción",
    "questionDetails": "La canción de Hiawatha.",
    "answer": "song",
    "answerDetails": "The Song of Hiawatha."
  },
  {
    "id": 1194,
    "question": "hablemos",
    "questionDetails": "Yo digo que hablemos con el director.",
    "answer": "talk",
    "answerDetails": "I say we talk to the warden."
  },
  {
    "id": 1195,
    "question": "ley",
    "questionDetails": "El Parlamento aprobó la ley.",
    "answer": "act, legislation, statute",
    "answerDetails": "The act was approved by Parliament."
  },
  {
    "id": 1196,
    "question": "guapa",
    "questionDetails": "Me han dicho que es muy guapa.",
    "answer": "pretty, beautiful, cute",
    "answerDetails": "They say she’s very pretty."
  },
  {
    "id": 1197,
    "question": "veas",
    "answer": "see"
  },
  {
    "id": 1198,
    "question": "hables",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que me hables o que escuches.",
    "answer": "talk, speak",
    "answerDetails": "I want you to talk or listen."
  },
  {
    "id": 1199,
    "question": "presentar",
    "questionDetails": "Se les ordenó a los soldados que presentaran armas.",
    "answer": "present, submit, introduce",
    "answerDetails": "The soldiers were commanded to present arms."
  },
  {
    "id": 1200,
    "question": "escucho",
    "questionDetails": "De vez en cuando escucho sobre cómo te está yendo.",
    "answer": "hear, listen",
    "answerDetails": "I once in a while hear how you are doing."
  }
]